Hello everyone, welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Katherine and today we're talking about something that I haven't actually seen
我是Katherine，今天我们聊的话题是我很久没见到、
in a long time but is very common in the States, especially in suburban areas.
但在美国很常见的东西，尤其是在郊区。
That's right.
没错。
We're going to get a subscription as the title of the lesson says.
就像课程标题说的，我们要订阅东西。
So we're going to subscribe to magazines, newspapers, stuff like that.
我们要订阅杂志、报纸之类的。
So there's a guy coming around to everyone's houses and he's offering different magazine
有个人挨家挨户上门，
subscriptions.
推销各种杂志订阅。
So let's take a listen to today's dialogue and we'll be back in a moment to talk about
那我们先听一下今天的对话，
what's going on.
稍后再回来讨论内容。
Good afternoon, ma'am.
下午好，女士。
My name is Mike and I'm selling subscriptions to all sorts of periodicals.
我叫Mike，我在推销各种期刊的订阅。
No, thank you.
不了，谢谢。
I'm not interested.
我不感兴趣。
Please, ma'am, if you could spare five minutes of your time, I'm sure we could find something
拜托了，女士，如果您能抽出五分钟时间，
that could interest you.
我肯定能找到让您感兴趣的东西。
I wish I could, but I have to walk the dog and finish cooking.
我也想，但我得遛狗还要做完饭。
So if you'd excuse me.
所以请见谅。
We have a great variety of magazines all about cooking.
我们有很多关于烹饪的杂志。
This one, for example, is a bi-monthly publication with recipes from all over the world.
比如这本，是一本双月刊，里面有来自世界各地的食谱。
Wow.
哇。
Well, that would be kind of useful.
嗯，那还挺有用的。
Do you have any other cooking magazines?
你还有其他烹饪杂志吗？
Sure do.
当然有。
This one is a quarterly publication, but each issue has over 200 colored pages of recipes
这本是季刊，但每期都有超过200页的彩色食谱，
and also many home decorating ideas.
还有很多家居装饰的点子。
Wow, this is nice.
哇，这本真不错。
Okay, sign me up for both publications.
好的，这两本我都订了。
You mentioned you have a dog.
你提到你养了一只狗。
Can pet owners sign up for this weekly newsletter that has information on dog care, pet shops,
宠物主人可以订阅这份每周通讯吗？里面有关于狗狗护理、宠物店，
and even pet sitters?
甚至宠物保姆的信息？
That's exactly what I needed.
这正是我需要的。
What else do you have?
你还有什么别的？
Well, I also have...
嗯，我还有……
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So as you saw, Mike is, well, not very excited to be selling subscriptions, but he has magazines
所以就像你看到的，迈克其实不太热衷于卖订阅，但他几乎什么杂志都有，
about almost everything, I think.
我觉得。
That's right.
没错。
And he's actually a pretty good salesperson because it sounds like this customer is going
而且他其实是个挺不错的销售员，因为听起来这位顾客打算
to buy quite a few magazines.
买不少杂志。
Exactly.
没错。
And so he used a lot of interesting vocabulary related to magazines and subscriptions.
所以他用了很多与杂志和订阅相关的有趣词汇。
So let's take a look at those now in Language Takeaway.
现在让我们在“语言要点”环节看看这些内容。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
Okay, so this first word is one that we've already said a couple of times in today's
好的，那么第一个词就是我们今天已经说过好几次的。
lesson.
抱歉，您没有提供具体的字幕内容。请提供需要翻译的 EnglishPod 字幕内容（包括每个 cue 的 id 和英文文本），我将按照您的要求进行专业的中英翻译。
This is the topic of the lesson.
这是本节课的主题。
The word is subscription.
这个词是“订阅”。
Okay, so if you get a subscription, that means that you are paying money to receive something
好的，如果你订阅了，那就意味着你付钱来接收某些东西。
every month, every week, etc.
每个月、每周等等。
That's right.
没错。
So the time is fixed.
所以时间定下来了。
Like you said, it could be weekly, the time could change.
就像你说的，可能是每周一次，时间也可能变动。
But basically, you have a promise that after you pay this money, you'll receive something
但基本上，你付了这笔钱后，就能保证收到某样东西。
periodically.
定期地。
Right.
好的。
And so there are many things that you could have a subscription for, not just magazines.
所以有很多东西你都可以订阅，不仅仅是杂志。
Newspapers come in subscriptions.
报纸是通过订阅来获取的。
That's right.
没错。
Or maybe you pay for satellite TV.
或者你可能付费看卫星电视。
That's a subscription.
那就是订阅。
You pay every month and you receive channels, like lots of channels.
你每个月付钱，然后收到频道，很多频道。
Exactly.
没错。
Or hopefully, EnglishPod, you receive by subscription or you pay the subscription fee.
或者，希望是EnglishPod，你通过订阅来接收，或者支付订阅费。
Exactly.
没错。
So with EnglishPod, you subscribe.
所以对于EnglishPod，你订阅。
That would be the verb.
那是动词形式。
A subscription is the noun.
订阅是名词形式。
You subscribe to a service like a newspaper magazine and you receive the magazine or the
你订阅一项服务，比如报纸杂志，然后你收到杂志或
service every month, every week, every day, depending on what the subscription is like.
服务，每月、每周、每天，取决于订阅的类型。
Okay, and so because subscriptions come at different time frames, so for example, EnglishPod,
好的，因为订阅有不同的时间周期，比如EnglishPod，
we have lessons three times a week.
我们每周发布三次课程。
Newspapers are oftentimes every day.
报纸通常是每天发布。
They come in different periods of time.
它们在不同时间段送达。
So we call these kinds of publications periodicals.
所以我们称这类出版物为期刊。
Okay.
好的。
So for example, as you said, a newspaper, it comes every day.
比如，就像你说的，报纸每天出版。
That's the period of time.
那就是时间周期。
So it's a periodical.
所以它是期刊。
The same as a magazine.
和杂志一样。
Sometimes they are weekly.
有时它们是周刊。
Sometimes they are monthly.
有时它们是月刊。
Is a book a periodical, Pop Quiz?
书是期刊吗，小测验？
No.
不是。
Okay.
好的。
No, because you only get it once.
不是，因为你只得到一次。
Right.
对。
So basically, a periodical has to be something, I guess, that comes out every so often, a
所以基本上，期刊必须是某种定期出版的东西，一个
new version, a new edition.
新版本，新一期。
It's continually updating.
它不断更新。
Okay.
好的。
So that is periodicals and subscriptions.
这就是期刊和订阅。
Now moving on to when he was trying to sell the magazines, he said, we have a great variety
现在继续讲到他试图卖杂志时，他说，我们有各种各样的
of magazines all about cooking.
关于烹饪的杂志。
So what is a variety?
那么什么是“variety”？
Variety is a great word.
“Variety”是个很棒的词。
It's a word I personally am a very big fan of.
我个人非常喜欢这个词。
I like to have many choices to choose from.
我喜欢有很多选择可以挑选。
So variety means something that has many options.
所以“variety”意味着有很多选项的东西。
For example, at the grocery store, there's a great variety of food.
例如，在杂货店里，有各种各样的食物。
There are apples and crackers and cakes and wine.
有苹果、饼干、蛋糕和葡萄酒。
So variety means there are many different kinds of something.
所以“variety”意味着某样东西有很多不同的种类。
Okay.
好的。
So many choices.
所以很多选择。
At the bookstore, you can find a variety of books and magazines, for example.
例如，在书店里，你可以找到各种各样的书和杂志。
All right.
好的。
Now moving on to, again, when we're talking about the period of time, how often she's
现在继续讲，当我们谈论时间段时，她多久
going to get this cooking magazine, the one that he's showing her is a bi-monthly publication.
会收到这本烹饪杂志，他给她看的那本是双月刊。
So what exactly does it mean if she receives a magazine bi-monthly?
那么，如果她双月收到一本杂志，到底是什么意思？
Okay.
好的。
So this is a bit confusing in English.
这在英语中有点令人困惑。
Bi-monthly has two meanings, but what's important is the word bi- here or the prefix bi-.
“Bi-monthly”有两个意思，但重要的是这里的“bi-”这个词或前缀“bi-”。
That means two.
那意味着“二”。
Okay.
好的。
So we could say bi-monthly, bi-weekly, bi-annually.
所以我们可以说“bi-monthly”、“bi-weekly”、“bi-annually”。
These all mean two.
这些都意味着“二”。
So in this case, we're talking about something that I receive two times every month.
所以在这种情况下，我们说的是我每个月收到两次的东西。
Okay.
好的。
Or it can be that you get it once every two months.
或者也可以是你每两个月收到一次。
Okay.
好的。
So that might be confusing.
所以这可能会让人困惑。
Right.
对。
So let's just say that it's the month of October and I have this great subscription to a magazine.
那么假设现在是十月，我订阅了一本很棒的杂志。
So in October, I will receive it two times.
所以在十月，我会收到两次。
Exactly.
正是。
So you get it twice.
所以你收到两次。
Or it could also mean that you receive the magazine in October and then you don't receive
或者也可以意味着你在十月收到杂志，然后直到十二月才收到
another magazine until December.
另一本杂志。
So it's a bi-monthly publication.
所以这是一本双月刊。
Every other month.
每隔一个月。
Every two months.
每两个月。
Right.
对。
So this is very confusing for us.
所以这对我们来说非常令人困惑。
It's confusing for you, but if you see this word bi-monthly or bi-weekly, you should ask
这对你来说很困惑，但如果你看到“bi-monthly”或“bi-weekly”这个词，你应该问
the person who's offering the subscription what kind they mean.
提供订阅的人他们指的是哪种。
Is it every month two times or is it every other month?
是每个月两次还是每隔一个月？
All right.
好的。
So exactly.
正是。
Just remember the prefix bi- means two.
只要记住前缀“bi-”意味着“二”。
And then if it's bi-monthly, bi-annual, bi-weekly, you have to more or less make sure that they
然后如果是“bi-monthly”、“bi-annual”、“bi-weekly”，你或多或少要确保他们
specify what they mean because it can mean both.
明确说明他们的意思，因为它可以表示两种意思。
And that's how ambiguous this word is.
这个词就是这么模棱两可。
It is.
是的。
So the next one, the next word we have for you is not nearly as confusing.
所以下一个，我们为你准备的下一个词就没那么令人困惑了。
It's a very, very common word in both periodicals and sales, but also in marketing and business
这是一个在期刊和销售中，也在市场营销和商业中非常非常常见的词
as well.
也是如此。
Right.
对。
We're talking about a quarterly publication or something that comes out once every quarter.
我们说的是季刊或每季度出版一次的东西。
Right.
对。
So if you think about a year, a year has 12 months.
所以如果你考虑一年，一年有12个月。
A quarter of a year is three months.
一年的四分之一是三个月。
So the first quarter is January, February, March.
所以第一季度是一月、二月、三月。
Exactly.
正是。
So a quarterly publication means that you will get a magazine four times in one year.
所以季刊意味着你一年会收到四次杂志。
Okay.
好的。
We could also talk about quarterly sales.
我们也可以谈论季度销售。
You know, this quarter our business did very well, but last quarter was not so good.
你知道，这个季度我们的生意很好，但上个季度不太好。
So quarter means three months at a time.
所以“quarter”意味着一次三个月。
Exactly.
没错。
And for our last word on language takeaway today, we are talking about a weekly newsletter.
今天语言学习的最后一个词，我们要讨论的是“每周简报”。
So weekly is pretty straightforward.
“每周”这个词很直接。
You receive it once every week.
你每周收到一次。
That's right.
对。
So weekly publications are very common.
所以每周出版物很常见。
What is a newsletter?
什么是简报？
A newsletter is important in periodicals because it's not a magazine, but it's not a letter
简报在期刊中很重要，因为它既不是杂志，也不是信件，
either.
也不是。
It's basically a short update, a couple of pages maybe, or even one page that's on a
它基本上是一份简短的更新，可能只有几页，甚至一页，
piece of paper that gives you information about a group or a club or a community.
印在纸上，提供关于某个团体、俱乐部或社区的信息。
For example, we could say the EnglishPod newsletter comes out quarterly.
比如，我们可以说EnglishPod的简报是每季度出版一次。
Exactly.
没错。
Maybe in your offices you receive your company's newsletter.
也许在你的办公室里，你会收到公司的简报。
So usually some companies will come out with a monthly or a quarterly newsletter where
所以通常有些公司会每月或每季度出一份简报，
if you have many offices or many branches all over the country or the world, then you
如果你在全国或全球有很多办公室或分支机构，
will receive updates or news about what's going on in other places within your same
你就会收到关于同一公司其他地方
company.
最新动态或新闻的更新。
That's right.
对。
So these are very useful for communication across the company.
所以这些对于公司内部的沟通非常有用。
You can tell some people in your New York office that in Los Angeles we have a new cafeteria
你可以告诉纽约办公室的同事，洛杉矶有了新的食堂
or a new employee.
或新员工。
Exactly.
没错。
So that is what a newsletter is basically for.
所以这就是简报的主要用途。
I think it's time now for us to listen to the dialogue again and we'll be back to talk
我想现在是时候再听一遍对话了，之后我们会回来
to you with four key phrases on Fluency Builder right after this.
在流利度构建环节中，和你们聊聊四个关键短语。
Good afternoon ma'am.
下午好，女士。
My name is Mike and I'm selling subscriptions to all sorts of periodicals.
我叫迈克，我在销售各种期刊的订阅。
No, thank you.
不了，谢谢。
I'm not interested.
我不感兴趣。
Please ma'am, if you could spare five minutes of your time, I'm sure we could find something
女士，请听我说，如果您能抽出五分钟时间，我肯定能找到
that could interest you.
让您感兴趣的东西。
I wish I could, but I have to walk the dog and finish cooking, so if you'd excuse me.
我希望我能，但我得遛狗和做饭，所以请原谅我。
We have a great variety of magazines all about cooking.
我们有各种各样的烹饪杂志。
This one for example is a bi-monthly publication with recipes from all over the world.
比如这本，是双月刊，里面有来自世界各地的食谱。
Wow, well that would be kind of useful.
哇，那还挺有用的。
Do you have any other cooking magazines?
你还有其他烹饪杂志吗？
Sure do.
当然有。
This one is a quarterly publication, but each issue has over 200 colored pages of recipes
这本是季刊，但每期有超过200页的彩色食谱，
and also many home decorating ideas.
还有很多家居装饰创意。
Wow, this is nice.
哇，这本不错。
Okay, sign me up for both publications.
好的，给我订这两本吧。
You mentioned you have a dog.
你提到你养了狗。
Most pet owners sign up for this weekly newsletter that has information on dog care, pet shops
大多数宠物主人都会订阅这份每周简报，里面有关于狗狗护理、宠物店
and even pet sitters.
甚至宠物保姆的信息。
That's exactly what I needed.
这正是我需要的。
What else do you have?
你还有什么？
Well, I also have...
嗯，我还有……
All right, so now we have some sentences or ways that you can say things on Fluency Builder.
好了，现在我们在流利度构建环节中有一些句子或表达方式。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
Okay, this first phrase is very, very common among sales and sales people because basically
好的，第一个短语在销售和销售人员中非常非常常见，因为基本上
it's a way to be polite and to ask someone to listen to you for a little while.
这是一种礼貌的方式，请求别人听你说一会儿。
The salesperson says, if you could spare five minutes of your time.
销售人员说：“如果您能抽出五分钟时间。”
Okay, so let's start with that part.
好的，我们先从这部分开始。
If you could spare.
“如果您能抽出。”
So to spare something means do you have something extra?
所以“抽出”某物意思是，你有多余的东西吗？
Do you have enough of it?
你有足够的吗？
Yeah, so I could say, can you spare $5?
是的，所以我可以问：“你能借我五美元吗？”
I forgot my wallet at home.
我把钱包忘在家里了。
So that means do you have an extra $5 I could borrow?
所以意思是，你有多余的五美元可以借我吗？
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
So if you're asking someone to spare five minutes of their time, you're asking them
所以如果你请别人抽出五分钟时间，你是在请求他们
to give you five minutes of their time.
给你五分钟时间。
That's right.
对。
So if you could spare a second or if you could spare five minutes of your time, I would like
所以如果你能抽出一秒钟或五分钟时间，我想
to talk to you.
和你谈谈。
Okay, so it's a very polite way to ask someone for their time.
好的，这是一种非常礼貌的请求别人时间的方式。
Now for our next phrase, the woman is also very polite.
现在看下一个短语，那位女士也非常礼貌。
She says, you know what?
她说：“你知道吗？”
I have to walk the dog.
“我得遛狗。”
I have to finish cooking.
“我得做完饭。”
So if you would excuse me.
“所以请原谅我。”
She's basically saying no in a very polite way.
她基本上是在用一种非常礼貌的方式说“不”。
If you could excuse me, I've got to go.
“如果你能原谅我，我得走了。”
So this is a kind of a very indirect but polite way of saying, I'm sorry, I can't stay.
所以这是一种非常间接但礼貌的方式说：“对不起，我不能待了。”
I got to go or I can't really talk to you right now.
“我得走了”或“我现在不能和你说话。”
That's right.
对。
So if you're at a party, for example, and you're talking to somebody, but you don't
所以如果你在派对上，比如，你在和某人聊天，但你不想
really want to talk to them anymore, you could say, it was nice talking to you if you could
再聊下去了，你可以说：“很高兴和你聊天，如果你能
excuse me.
原谅我。”
It means if I can leave now.
它的意思是，我现在能不能离开。
Okay, so you can say if you could excuse me or if you would excuse me.
好的，所以你可以说“if you could excuse me”或“if you would excuse me”。
Both forms are pretty much the same.
两种形式差不多一样。
Okay, and what about when she actually is convinced about the magazine?
好的，那当她真的被那本杂志说服时呢？
She says, wow, this is nice.
她说，哇，这本真不错。
Okay, sign me up for both publications.
好的，给我订阅两种刊物。
Okay, sign me up.
好的，算我一个。
This means I would like a subscription.
这意味着我想要订阅。
That means I would like you to take my information and I will give you some money.
这意味着我希望你记下我的信息，我会付钱。
But this is also a really nice phrase in English because it means I want to do this.
但这也是英语中一个很棒的短语，因为它表示我想做这件事。
I'm interested.
我很感兴趣。
So if you would use this in another context, for example, a group of friends are going
所以如果你在另一个场景中使用它，比如一群朋友要
to the movies.
去看电影。
I say, oh, sign me up.
我说，哦，算我一个。
I want to go.
我想去。
I heard that movie was awesome.
我听说那部电影很棒。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
So sign me up is like include me, I want to go to or I'm part of it, of whatever you're
所以“sign me up”就像包括我，我想参与或成为其中一部分，无论你在
doing.
做什么。
Exactly.
没错。
Okay, so that's all the phrases we have for you today.
好的，这就是我们今天为你准备的所有短语。
I think they're really good.
我觉得它们都很好。
They're not specific for this circumstance of getting a subscription.
它们并不只适用于订阅这种特定情况。
As we saw, we can use them in many other situations.
正如我们所见，我们可以在很多其他场合使用它们。
So I think we should go back, listen to the dialogue for the last time and we'll be back
所以我认为我们应该回去，再听一遍对话，然后回来
to talk a little bit more.
再聊一会儿。
Good afternoon, ma'am.
下午好，女士。
My name is Mike and I'm selling subscriptions to all sorts of periodicals.
我叫迈克，我在推销各种期刊的订阅。
No, thank you.
不了，谢谢。
I'm not interested.
我不感兴趣。
Please, ma'am, if you could spare five minutes of your time, I'm sure we could find something
拜托，女士，如果您能抽出五分钟时间，我肯定能找到一些
that could interest you.
让您感兴趣的东西。
I wish I could, but I have to walk the dog and finish cooking.
我希望可以，但我得遛狗和做完饭。
So if you'd excuse me.
所以请原谅我。
We have a great variety of magazines all about cooking.
我们有各种各样的烹饪杂志。
This one, for example, is a bi-monthly publication with recipes from all over the world.
比如这本，是一本双月刊，里面有来自世界各地的食谱。
Wow.
哇。
Well, that would be kind of useful.
嗯，那还挺有用的。
Do you have any other cooking magazines?
你还有其他烹饪杂志吗？
Sure do.
当然有。
This one is a quarterly publication, but each issue has over 200 colored pages of recipes
这本是季刊，但每期有超过200页的彩色食谱
and also many home decorating ideas.
和许多家居装饰创意。
Wow, this is nice.
哇，这本真不错。
Okay, sign me up for both publications.
好的，给我订阅两种刊物。
You mentioned you have a dog.
你提到你养了狗。
Most pet owners sign up for this weekly newsletter that has information on dog care, pet shops
大多数宠物主人会订阅这份周报，里面有关于狗护理、宠物店
and even pet sitters.
甚至宠物保姆的信息。
That's exactly what I needed.
这正是我需要的。
What else do you have?
你还有什么？
Well, I also have...
嗯，我还有……
All right, so subscriptions, periodicals, all this is very common, as you said, in the
好了，所以订阅、期刊，这些在美国都很常见，就像你说的。
United States.
美国。
People get them through the mail every month, right?
人们每个月通过邮件收到它们，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
And I have to say, it's changing now.
而且我得说，现在情况在变化。
You know, we used to get subscriptions at home when I was a kid.
你知道，我小时候家里经常订阅。
We'd have magazine subscriptions and even a newspaper subscription.
我们会订杂志，甚至订报纸。
But these days, people are doing more and more on the internet.
但现在，人们越来越多地在网上做这些事。
So you don't see the guy with the subscriptions coming from, you know, going from door to
所以你很少看到推销订阅的人挨家挨户
door to sell you this.
上门推销。
You do it yourself on the internet.
你自己在网上操作。
So it's pretty common that way.
所以这种方式很常见。
Do you have any web subscriptions?
你有任何网络订阅吗？
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
I haven't signed up for any periodicals on the web.
我没有在网上订阅任何期刊。
I do receive the newspaper every day and that's about it.
我每天收报纸，仅此而已。
It's kind of hard to receive magazines where we are, but I am a big fan of magazines like
在我们这里收杂志有点难，但我很喜欢像《国家地理》或《大众机械》这样的杂志。
National Geographic or Popular Mechanics.
我小时候就有。
I had that when I was a kid.
My grandmother would always give us a subscription to National Geographic for Christmas.
我奶奶总是送我们一份《国家地理》的订阅作为圣诞礼物。
It's a very good magazine and it's so colorful, full of pictures and really interesting articles,
那是一本非常好的杂志，色彩丰富，充满图片和非常有趣的文章，
not only about animals, but about the world in general.
不仅关于动物，还关于整个世界。
So it's really cool.
所以真的很酷。
That's right.
没错。
And they always gave you a map that you could take out and open up and it was the best part
而且他们总是附赠一张地图，你可以拿出来展开，那是整本杂志
of the whole magazine.
最棒的部分。
Exactly.
没错。
So actually, I really enjoy having subscriptions to periodicals, magazines, newspapers.
所以实际上，我很喜欢订阅期刊、杂志、报纸。
Not a big fan of newsletters or things on the internet.
不太喜欢网上的新闻简报之类的东西。
I kind of like to hold a magazine or take it with me if I'm on a trip.
我比较喜欢拿着杂志，或者旅行时带着它。
Yeah, I totally agree.
是啊，我完全同意。
So yeah, but I think many of our listeners may have a subscription to their local newspaper,
所以，是的，但我觉得很多听众可能订阅了当地的报纸，
local magazines, or maybe as you said, internet subscriptions.
本地杂志，或者像你说的，网络订阅。
I know some people sign up for the Harvard Business Review that's available online or
我知道有些人订阅了《哈佛商业评论》，它有在线版，
even I think the New York Times has an online platform.
甚至《纽约时报》也有在线平台。
They do.
确实有。
So you should let us know what subscriptions do you have, what periodicals do you like
所以你应该告诉我们你订阅了什么，喜欢读哪些期刊，
to read.
喜欢读什么。
Our website of course is EnglishPod.com.
我们的网站当然是 EnglishPod.com。
You can also purchase a subscription there.
你也可以在那里购买订阅。
We hope to see you on the website and until next time.
我们希望在网站上见到你，下次再见。
All right.
好的。
Bye.
再见。